http://www.popham-airfield.co.uk/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyKey detailsThis website privacy policy describes how Charles Church Spitfires Ltd. protects and makes use of the information you give the company when you use this website.If you are asked to provide information when using this website, it will only be used in the ways described in this privacy policy.This policy is updated from time to time. The latest version is published on this page.This website privacy policy was updated on:   1st October 2017If you have any questions about this policy, please email pophamairfield@btconnect.com or write to:The ManagerCharles Church Spitfires Ltd.Popham AirfieldCoxford DownNr. WinchesterSO21 3BDWe may gather and use certain information about individuals in order to provide products and services and to enable certain functions on this website.We may also collect information to better understand how visitors use this website and to present timely, relevant information to them.We may collect the following information:•    Name and job title•    Contact information including email address•    Demographic information, such as postcode, preferences and interests•    Website usage data•    Other information relevant to client enquiries•    Other information pertaining to special offers and surveysCollecting this data helps us understand what you are looking from the company, enabling us to deliver improved products and services.  Specifically, we may use data:•    For our own internal records.•    To improve the products and services we provide.•    To contact you in response to a specific enquiry.
Privacy Policy                    Terms of Use                    Copyright Statement
Contact info Tel:
01256 397733Email: mike@popham-airfield.co.ukPopham Airfield, Coxford Down, Winchester, SO21 3BD
Follow us
Share by:
